{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the capital city of Morocco?",
      "options": ["Casablanca", "Rabat", "Marrakech", "Fez"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which mountain range extends across the northwestern part of Morocco?",
      "options": [
        "Himalayas",
        "Andes Mountains",
        "Atlas Mountains",
        "Rocky Mountains"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which ocean lies to the west of Morocco?",
      "options": [
        "Atlantic Ocean",
        "Pacific Ocean",
        "Arctic Ocean",
        "Indian Ocean"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the traditional Moroccan dish made from semolina?",
      "options": ["Sushi", "Burger", "Couscous", "Pizza"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which famous city in Morocco is known for its blue-painted buildings?",
      "options": ["Tangier", "Essaouira", "Chefchaouen", "Agadir"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the currency of Morocco?",
      "options": ["Dirham", "Euro", "Dollar", "Pound"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which desert stretches across the southeastern part of Morocco?",
      "options": [
        "Gobi Desert",
        "Sahara Desert",
        "Atacama Desert",
        "Kalahari Desert"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which river flows through the capital city of Morocco?",
      "options": [
        "Nile River",
        "Amazon River",
        "Mississippi River",
        "Bouregreg River"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the official language of Morocco?",
      "options": ["Arabic", "English", "French", "Spanish"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Moroccan city is famous for its annual International Film Festival?",
      "options": ["Casablanca", "Tangier", "Marrakech", "Agadir"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    }
  ]
}
